<resources>
   <string name="app_name">PAMO PROJECT</string>
   <string name="enter_amount">Enter data</string>
   <string name="tip_percentage">15%</string>
   <string name="tip">Tip</string>
   <string name="total">Total</string>
   <string name="weight">Your weight</string>
   <string name="height">Your height</string>
   <string name="bmi">Your BMI </string>
   <string name="button_1">BMICalculator</string>
   <string name="button_2">PPMCalculator</string>
   <string name="button_3">Food recipes</string>
   <string name="button_4">BMI calculator History</string>
   <string name="button_5">Simple Quiz</string>
   <string name="cal_weight_input">Your weight(kg)</string>
   <string name="cal_height_input">Your height(cm)</string>
   <string name="cal_age_input">Your age(years)</string>
   <string name="cal_gender_input">Male = 0/Female = 1</string>
   <string name="cal_calories_calculated">Calculated PPM</string>
   <string name="gender_male">M</string>
   <string name="gender_female">F</string>
   <string name="recipe_1">
         "Fluffy Pancakes\n
   Ingredients: 1 1/2 cups all-purpose flour, 3 1/2 teaspoons baking powder, 1/2 teaspoon salt, 1 tablespoon sugar, 1 1/4 cups milk, 1 egg, 3 tablespoons melted butter\n

   In a large mixing bowl, combine the flour, baking powder, salt, and sugar.\n
   In a separate bowl, whisk together the milk, egg, and melted butter.\n
   Pour the wet mixture into the dry mixture and stir until just combined. It's okay if there are a few lumps.\n
   Heat a non-stick griddle or skillet over medium heat. Scoop 1/4 cup of batter onto the griddle for each pancake.\n
   Cook the pancakes until bubbles form on the surface, then flip and cook for another 1-2 minutes until golden brown.\n
   Remove the pancakes from the griddle and serve warm with your favorite toppings, such as maple syrup, fresh fruit, or whipped cream."
       </string>
   <string name="recipe_2">
      "How to Make Banana Bread \n
      Ingredients: Flour, baking soda, salt, butter, brown sugar, eggs, bananas \n
      1. Combine the dry ingredients in one bowl.\n
      2. Beat the butter and sugar in another bowl. Add the eggs and mashed bananas. \n
      3. Add the wet mixture to the dry mixture. \n
      4. Pour the batter into a loaf pan and bake in a preheated oven. "
   </string>
   <string name="quiz_question_1">Is social media the only way to meeting new people?</string>
   <string name="quiz_question_2">Can practicing regular meditation help alleviate stress and enhance mental well-being?</string>
   <string name="quiz_question_3">Does excessive screen time have a negative impact on the quality of sleep?</string>
   <string name="quiz_question_4">Are organic foods worth the higher cost for their potential health benefits?</string>
   <string name="quiz_question_5">Can practicing gratitude on a daily basis enhance overall happiness and well-being?</string>
   <string name="quiz_question_6">Is regular physical exercise important for maintaining a healthy weight?</string>
</resources>
